I saw the notices this morning.
But if you wanted to help your mama out.
Franklin ain't no savior.
You willing to lose this house?
Yes. I would fucking lose this house.
Your days of slaving for
that Jheri curl motherfucker
are over.
Wanna come work for us?
Oh. my God. Franklin. I
will not let you down.
Just keep it to yourself. all right?
We're a family here. Got to have trust.
I know it's hard to let someone in
after what happened to this family.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
[GUNSHOT]
_
[SHOTGUN BLASTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
She's a fucking cop.
What does that make Pedro?
Still nothing?
I'd be a lot less calm if there were.
The real prize here is
pilot and his partner.
We get them and we've got
a shot at the Colombians.
Well. we'd be happy to take the weight.
Make up the difference next time.
I like this guy.
_
The people I use.
they don't get their money.
it's your name I'm giving them.
- Hey. man. office.
- Don't look at it.
Just keep your eyes straight ahead.
Somebody's watching the office.
You gonna tell me the truth or
keep feeding me shit. puta?
What if I can offer you the recipe?
The Monarcas want your head.
I won't be able to hold
them off for long.
Delroy's dead. Vic is dead.
They castrated them!
- [GROANING]
- [GASPS]
Wanna know who killed your friends?
We can take you right to him.
And why would you do that?
'Cause you're gonna tell us
how to cook up that rock.
I look forward to hearing from you soon.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Hey. Sosa.
Let's get this straight now.
I never fuck anybody over in my life
who didn't have it coming.
You got that?
Hey. why he talk like that?
He from Cuba.
Ain't they all from Cuba?
I don't break them for no one.
Do you understand?
See. that's what we need.
Constitution... rule book or some shit.
That'll be the first commandment.
Hey. Saint. words is just words. man.
Boss is boss.
[CHUCKLES] That ain't true.
Hey. shut up. man!
Hey. you shut the fuck up!
- I'm trying to watch this fucking movie.
- Quiet down!
- [LAUGHTER]
- Hey. can y'all be quiet?
Hey. how many times you seen this shit?
I don't know. like. five times.
Bolivia. Fuck. see what I mean?
They got that whole production line.
All right. so that means you expert.
If they all from Cuba.
why he the only one that talk like that?
Man. will y'all shut up?
Man. this is why I don't go
to the movies with y'all.
Y'all worse than my
mother fucking Auntie.
We don't go to the
movies with you. nigga.
'cause you buy a box of Lemonheads.
suck the color off of them.
you spit the motherfuckers
back in the box.
Been known yo ass since Audubon.
never did understand
why you do that shit.
- Whatever. nigga! Shut up!
- Shit's nasty. It's nasty.
This is why I don't go
nowhere with y'all.
- It's weird.
- [LAUGHS]
That's what I'm talking about.
Too many places in that movie.
Yeah. and we ain't been
to not one of them.
[LAUGHS] Can you believe this shit?
I don't even have a fucking passport.
I keep a strict policy. I
don't go past Crenshaw.
[LAUGHS]
Ronald Reagan's a lie.
Swear to God he is.
Ronald Reagan is a lie.
Yeah. I swear to God he is.
Gimme your keys.
Nah. cuz. I'm good.
Yeah. homey. end up in
the valley or some shit.
Nah. man. we won't. Come on.
Give 'em here.
Everybody should know he's a lie.
I don't like not knowing
where I'm going. Saint.
Ronald Reagan's a lie!
We gonna be all right.
Ronald Reagan's a lie.
Swear to God he is.
I'm not getting in the back.
I ain't doing this with you today.
You the tallest so you
gotta go in the back.
Yeah. but you need the most leg room.
Oh. so y'all wanna talk shit?
All right.
Swear to God he is.
["LOW RIDER RAP" BY
POOR BOY RAPPERS PLAYS]
♪ Just give us a beat and
we'll pass the test ♪
♪ We're gonna make you down
from your head to your toes ♪
♪ Turn up the stereos and here we go ♪
♪ Now early one day I
got the urge to drive ♪
♪ So I took my mom's car for a joyride ♪
[SIGHS]
God damn.
[SEA GULLS CAWING]
[DISTANT SHOUTING]
[WAVES CRASHING]
Only time I ever seen
this when we used to
drive by them oil shit.
You know what I'm talking about?
A poor man's Disneyland.
Scare a nigga driving
this far Westside. Saint.
Whoo! It's cold as shit!
Uh-huh. they don't tell
you that part. huh?
Whoo!
Thought you was gonna have us jumped
by some Shoreline cats or something.
Hey. why is it bubbling?
- 'Cause of the crabs.
- What do you mean the crabs?
- [LAUGHTER]
- Fuck. man!
They small. man.
And they burrow in a different shell
when the old ones wear out.
Survival tactic.
National Geographic motherfucker.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
But listen. I wanted to tell y'all.
I know shit ain't been easy.
That I'm tougher on you than
you think I need to be.
It's only so when we expand
I can put y'all in charge.
Shit we got going on now. man?
It's just the beginning.
We just warming up.
We building an empire.
You feel me?
Huh?
Yeah.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Shit.
- Oh. shit!
I can't stand up!
[LAUGHTER]
Stop acting like a bitch. [LAUGHTER]
- It's cold for real though.
- Nigga. I know.
My feet are so fucking wet.
[LAUGHTER]
Yo ass can't swim.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
♪ ♪
[DOG BARKS]
Ahh.
Ahh. he likes you.
- Is that a dog?
- Yeah.
I figured we're being hunted.
It's a good time to adopt. Yeah.
He just showed up.
Back yard. No tags. Friendly though.
I'm sorry. you're feeding him?
Forget about the dog.
Where were you?
Huh? Did you find out who's after us?
It is the DEA.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
They called back a few hours after
the LAPD pinged their plates.
They weren't thrilled
that they were tracing
their vehicle. but yeah. DEA.
Huh.
So the DEA thinks we're drug dealers.
What are we gonna do?
Look. I have ways of
handling these situations.
[DOG SNEEZES]
Yeah? How?
'Cause you told me the CIA
isn't gonna protect us.
Based on how agitated the DEA agent was
when he called. how insistent they were
that the LAPD back off. my guess is
they got an undercover inside
the Villanueva operation.
You're saying that to me like
it's supposed to be good news.
It just sounds a lot worse.
Listen. this is what I'm trained to do.
Okay? I said I was going
to take care of it
and I will. but you're just
gonna have to trust me.
Okay?
[DOOR CREAKS]
Jesse motherfucking Jackson.
This nigga love pussy too
much to be president.
[LAUGHS] Guess that would get you
out the running too. huh?
Well. I have been blessed
with my sense of priorities.
These things got my ears swelling up.
Well. I wish yo ass would swell up.
Since I bought you that dress.
See. now you play too much.
Now what you got to say
some shit like that for?
Because I'm quick with mines. baby.
That's why you love me. right?
I ain't say all that.
Well. you don't have to.
My little country mouse.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Soft-ass Louie.
- What y'all doing out here?
- Something in that coffee
got you talking out yo neck.
It's something legendary. chile.
With you it always is.
Police raided Catch One again.
- [SIGHS] A mess.
- I know.
14K told me they was leaving them alone
'cause of that virus thing going around.
A mess.
So we throwing a ball for her. baby.
[LAUGHS]
You handling this without me?
Did I need your permission?
I'ma handle some business
that actually keeps this place open.
And the thing about
them earrings. baby...
the diamonds are real;
the backs are fake.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Damn.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
I got it.
Yeah.
You're kidding.
You try running a trace?
He said that?
Jesus Christ.
All right. give me the number.
I can't wait to hear this.
Mm-hmm.
I'll call you back.
- What was that?
- I don't know yet.
[TELEPHONE DIALS]
Hit it.
Hello?
I was told to call this number.
That you had some information for me?
Yeah. is this the agent
running the Villanueva case?
Who's this?
I'll offer you some free advice.
Pull your UC. walk away right now.
Look. hey. I'd love to believe you.
Take your word on this. but can we meet?
Discuss it in person?
This is your only warning.
If you ignore it. I'm not responsible
for what happens to your man.
And have a nice day.
Reed.
- 'Sup man.
- Thanks for coming.
Everything okay?
Yeah. just...
gonna have to shut down
business for a couple weeks.
Mind if I ask why?
Need some maintenance on the plane.
Some repairs and inspections
got to be made.
It's nothing major.
- You seem concerned.
- Nah.
It's just...
I've been thinking about expansion.
Yeah?
Like what? Like the valley?
How much you know about McDonald's?
- I'm sorry. what?
- You know. the restaurant.
Oh. uh...
I know enough to not to
call it a restaurant.
[LAUGHS]
Started by these two brothers.
The McDonald boys.
Figured out a way to better
mass produce the burger.
Ready seconds after you ordered.
Shit was like magic back then.
They came up with the idea.
but it was a man called Ray Kroc
who came up with the vision.
Started franchising McDonald's.
turned a better burger into an empire.
pushed the brothers out in the process.
Stole their name.
You want to talk about gangsta?
Al Capone ain't got shit on my man Ray.
So what... what are you saying?
That you want to start opening
McDonald's franchises?
Nah.
I didn't invent this rock.
But I'ma blow it up.
Detroit. D.C.
Chicago. Philly.
St. Louis. New York.
Huh?
Send a team of trusted
men to every city.
Set up a cook house. create the demand.
We'd be talking 50. 100 keys a week.
Lotta keys. [LAUGHS]
Yeah.
Well. you have as much
product from me as you need.
Promise you that.
Seems like you've given
this some real thought.
I've been thinking about
this my whole life.
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
Por favor. no. no. no. no.
[GROANS]
_
Is that your professional
medical opinion?
Doctor?
_
- [GROANS]
- [ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
Kevin?
No. Pinche Pedro.
- [GROANS]
- He's not gonna stop.
You know that.
[GROANS]
Page Kevin again.
Okay.
[TELEPHONE DIALS]
_
We don't know if Pedro
is a part of this.
I'm sorry you never got to use it.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
- [GROANS]
- [LAUGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Aye. aye. aye.
Hello?
Now I told you. stop paging me.
I just want to make sure you
haven't forgotten about us.
Yeah. like that's possible.
Time's running out.
Tomorrow morning. 10:00 a.m.
That's when we know where he'll be.
You want us to take you to him?
We need your answer by then.
Are Funyuns to onions what
pork rinds are to pork?
Not even close.
There's got to be some
science to this shit.
Don't even taste like onions.
They. Just. Chips.
Nigga. how you know?
He one bench press
away from Hulking out.
Since when do we bite this
hard on anonymous phone calls?
Since they know we have a UC inside.
If it was the Villanuevas
I'd be dead already. right?
Or they'd be ducking you like they are.
Hoping the phone call gets you pulled.
and if it doesn't.
they don't kill undercovers quickly.
You know who I think this is?
I think it's the suppliers.
The pilot and his partner.
I mean. think about it.
They make our surveillance.
Our plates get pinged.
And then we get this phone call.
Plates got pinged by LAPD.
So maybe that's who we're
looking at. Corrupt cops.
I mean. this call feels like.
a dirty cop move. doesn't it?
I don't know.
What I do know is it's got me spooked.
[DOOR OPENS]
On top of that. your 48 hours are up.
Tony. Come on. we are so close.
We got the APB out on them.
We're got their offices.
- It's only a matter of time...
- I'm sorry. but it's over.
We pick up the Villanuevas now.
We'll have to just keep
chasing the suppliers.
You did great.
You should be proud.
["I'VE JUST GOT TO FORGET YOU"
BY BOBBY PATTERSON PLAYS]
- ♪ One thing I've got to do ♪
- Aw.
♪ Whoa I know ♪
You look ten years younger.
Do I feel it.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
VA.
The benefits came through.
So we should have enough
if you'll have it.
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ It won't be easy ♪
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
- Thank you.
- ♪ Get you off of my mind ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
Thank you. Alton.
♪ ♪
Come here.
♪ It's just that bad ♪
Come on.
♪ I just gotta leave you. baby ♪
- What are you doing?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Nothing.
♪ I've just gotta put you down ♪
Mm-hmm. mm-hmm.
[LAUGHS] Okay.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
♪ I just gotta put you down ♪
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪ You see I sit down and I
thought about it. babe ♪
["BUFFALO GALS II" BY
MALCOLM MCLAREN PLAYS]
Hey. Lee. They here.
All right. Wanda. I can see that.
What's up. man?
- Grandma!
- She kinda goofy. huh?
Like the rest of these
motherfuckers here.
Hey. don't be like that. my nigga.
Get you something to drink and
- make yourselves at home.
- Oh. great advice. Professor Simmons.
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
♪ Two buffalo gals go
round the outside ♪
Hey. sugar.
♪ ♪
♪ Three buffalo gals
go round the outside ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪ ♪
Ooh.
♪ Four buffalo gals go
round the outside ♪
♪ Dosie doe your partners ♪
- Auntie. this is Franklin...
- What's going on. Wanda?
Huh?
You're really stealing
and selling my shit
- without telling me?
- She ain't steal.
Oh. so you knew about this shit?
I cooked the shit. I
can take what's mine.
You fuckin' high right now?
So what the fuck if I am?
It's my party. Franklin Saint.
AKA Mr. Fucking High And Mighty.
You can get the fuck out my house.
I don't want her anywhere
near the business.
Hey. Saint. Hey.
Hey. man. I told you
this was gonna happen.
Hey. Saint!
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Easy.
Hey. when we start yelling
at females in public?
You got a problem?
Yeah. I do. man. I ain't
put you up on that shit
so you can blow up her spot.
Well. maybe I need to enforce
some fucking discipline. Kev.
'Cause apparently I'm
running a daycare center.
[LAUGHS] So that's what
you think this is?
I know it.
What I know is you need
to make that shit right
with Leon and Wanda.
Who gives a fuck about Wanda?
♪ ♪
What?
Get back to your party.
♪ ♪
[CHEERING]
Ooh.
Children. Children. Children.
Hah. they can call us freaks.
but they can suffer for it.
But let's take a moment right now
and give it up for the one
who made tonight possible.
- Yay.
- [CHEERING]
Look at her.
She ain't gone. Louie girl.
Yeah!
Buy my sister a drink.
Okay? And me.
Laurent de Laurent.
Mmm.
We now give it up for Viola Pendarvis.
She all the way from New York City.
[SIGHS] Come on up here. girl.
Damn. bitch. my feet hurt.
- Well. ashy as they is.
- [LAUGHS]
You know you got them fault
lines in earthquake country.
- Hey. don't you even start with me...
- Start with you?
Honey. you knew I was gonna
read you from cover to cover.
Act like you know where to find a book.
I got the Good Book and my good sense.
Last time somebody tried
to baptize you. honey.
the water blew off.
[LAUGHTER]
Claudia. I don't know.
you over here counting
your blessings. but how you manage
to get a girl so quick-witted?
Yeah. baby. how you manage that?
I manage you. bitch.
Excuse me.
[LAUGHTER]
Laurent. you knew her
back in Watts. right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well. I must have found her after that.
when she was trying to
get out the sticks.
[LAUGHS]
Tricking for peanuts
outside of every motel
between Western and Figueroa.
Hey. listen. so what's wrong that?
Something strange for some change.
You know. it was her first job.
Claudia. you better chill.
Well. ain't no shame in it.
It's just the way she do it.
Fuck any old thing with a wallet.
Scraping by.
Something charming about a
little thing that desperate.
Don't know her own worth.
Well. that's where I come in.
See. I taught her
everything she need to know
about how to market her talents.
And. girl. she a savant. damn near.
Why you laying out all my business?
Ah. baby. I'm just joking with you.
Can't forget what built you.
Ooh. Damn.
Now you know. you cold as hell.
♪ ♪
What happened?
Look. I waited all day
outside the aviation office.
DEA surveillance didn't move
which means phone call
didn't scare 'em off. so...
Well. fuck.
- So what do we do now?
- First thing tomorrow morning.
we're gonna fly back east
and I'm gonna try a different tag.
Somebody else?
Avi called.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Here?
- A few hours ago.
How the fuck did Avi even
get this phone number?
I don't know. I didn't think to ask him.
Teddy. while he was
fucking threatening me.
- He was threatening you?
- The money for guns.
Says his guys have the arms.
We haven't sent the money.
Yeah. well. the money. or the...
the bulk of the money. anyway.
is in the aviation office.
Which is now under DEA surveillance.
Didn't sound like he was
fucking around. Teddy.
Yeah.
Sure he wasn't.
You wanna tell me what all that was?
What all that was over there
back at the thing and stuff?
You could be more specific.
- Use your words.
- Shitting on my name in front of Laurent.
- Did I lie?
- Fuck you.
You talk about me tricking in public.
Like I still do that shit.
Like I'm still that girl
walking down Figueroa.
- And you're not?
- No. the fuck I'm not.
Okay. Okay.
You big and bad as you want to be.
but you still that girl
when I have to put you in your place.
Trying to steal my club.
Ahh. this don't even make no damn sense.
- Don't play me.
- Claudia.
if I wanted your fucking club
I woulda been got it by now.
So this ain't about that.
Oh. yeah.
That little deal I cut with
Franklin for your piece of ass.
That's why we back here now.
You see?
- You don't change.
- That's old shit.
Why would I even waste my time?
Baby.
You don't think that I
could just want you?
No. [LAUGHS]
No. honey.
I don't trust no bitch who
used to sit on the steps
at the Snooty Fox waiting
for me to pick her ass up.
You just can't let it go. can you?
Old lady bitter
that I ain't your damn property no more.
That I just fucking chose you
and now you scared I'ma leave.
And that's what this is about.
Now hold up. Hold up. You get all. like.
mad at me and I'm the
only one keeping it real.
- No. I said I'm off this...
- What the fuck would you be without me?
What the fuck you say to me?
I said you a God damn joke.
You think I'm that pressed
by somebody I still pay for?
How you like that?
I'm funny now. bitch?
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[BLOW LANDS]
Oh. God.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[PANTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[TELEPHONE DIALS]
- Hey.
- Hey. it's me.
I need you to come to the club.
- All right. give me an hour.
- No. right the fuck now.
- All right.
- Okay. hurry up.
- Please.
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
We almost gave up on you.
Yeah. well. betraying your best friend
ain't exactly a quick decision.
Franklin will never know it was you.
Yeah. but I'll know it was me. won't I?
Shit.
How I even know you gonna
be me on the right. vato?
Not send me after one of your enemies?
I dealt with your little
cousin more than once.
He sold me the rock.
Turned me onto this whole thing.
The guy who killed him?
He's a fucking lunatic.
Only gonna 'cause
problems for all of us.
He is an enemy of mine.
I know how badly you want this.
Remember how upset you were at the park?
And I'm gonna be honest...
I was always surprised
Franklin didn't press me
to know who did it before shifting
the conversation back to business.
Nah. he did press you. and
you didn't do nothing.
You didn't know nothing.
You know what? Don't
fucking play me. chica.
We did know. amigo.
Franklin asked us to
find out before we met.
I knew. I just wouldn't give him up.
Bullshit.
Ask him yourself if
you don't believe us.
but I'm telling you the truth.
We can take you to him right now.
Or you can walk.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DOOR CREAKS]
She finally out.
I don't know why she don't
just go to the hospital.
She probably worried
Claudia'd be in the next bed over.
Claudia's a bad enemy to have. Unc.
Knows everything about us.
Has cops on the payroll.
Maybe you should be a little
less worried about Claudia.
a little bit more worried
about your Auntie.
I am worried about her.
One don't have shit
to do with the other.
Tomorrow I'ma find us a stash house.
Get everything criminal up out of here.
All right?
Mm-hmm.
Hey. Louie asking you
to handle that shit...
that mean she back?
Nigga. how the fuck I'm gonna know?
Get some rest.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ ♪
Shit.
Tell me I'm hallucinating this.
You're hallucinating this.
♪ ♪
Diego.
About fucking time.
We were thinking...
maybe you'd forgotten about your plane.
[DOG BARKING]
Hey. guys.
What are you doing here?
You canceled the pickup.
Again. You don't return our calls.
We don't have your address.
Lucky for us we have your tail numbers.
- Going somewhere?
- And taking your dog?
You running away on us. Reed?
Look. guys.
It's just a quick trip
to get the business back on track.
But. you know. if you're here...
you ought to find a nice hotel.
Just check in. hang out.
and we'll be back in a couple days.
Or maybe you should tell
us what the problem is.
Before we have a much
bigger fucking problem.
Look... uh...
We got some heat.
Fucking hate cops.
- We could help you with that.
- Take care of it real quick.
Completely unnecessary.
We just need a few days.
We're straightening it out.
Okay?
Fine.
You can go.
You can stay.
No.
- Yes.
Hey. guys. I have to fly him.
He can fly commercial.
- Go first class.
- We'll buy you a ticket.
No. we won't.
There's no chance of that.
Once you are ready to
resume our pickups.
Matt goes free.
Until then...
He's ours.
Wait. whoa. Whoa!
Get the fuck off him. Jesus.
Hey...
Fuck! All right. Hey.
Take care of my dog.
You better not fucking hurt him.
Don't fuck around with us. Reed.
Talk to you soon. eh?
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT MUTTERING]
What's on your mind?
I speak. I say my mind.
and somehow. someway
the exact opposite of what I say
turns out to be exactly
the way it happens.
Yeah. well. being black at the
bank will do that to you.
It's not funny.
Look. we still short?
God damn it. Alton. you know we're not.
[SIGHS]
Seems like all I have in my life
is a bunch of men who don't
listen to a word I say.
Cissy. what?
Standing in that damn bank
looking like a damn fool.
Smiling with our little bit of money.
Woman comes up to me.
tells me one Jason Peters
has paid off our mortgage.
Not one month. The whole thing.
Guess he going about it smart.
How is that smart?
- Franklin ain't right. Alton.
- The country ain't right. Cissy.
You know. and if he's
selling to grown folks.
then there's worse businesses
out there to be a part of.
This is not how I wanted
to own my own home.
This is my house. Mine!
Now it ain't even that.
Well. we'll make it right.
Here.
- Here.
- What...
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ ♪
Comes Saturday and Sunday afternoon.
Gets three hours supervised visitation.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
All right.
Let's go cook some rock.
You know I love that girl. right?
Love ain't my problem.
Well. you could say thank you instead of
dissing her in front of
her whole fucking family.
Thank you for stealing
and smoking my product.
To make you more money.
Threw the party just for that
even though she's already
fucking exhausted.
Then take a God damn nap.
All right. I'ma fucking handle it.
If anybody else in our crew
was taking rock. Leon.
smoking it...
Wouldn't be a fucking conversation.
You'd be focused on the business.
I hear you. a'ight?
But I think you worried
about the wrong shit.
And I think you ain't worry enough.
And that's the problem.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CAR TIRES ROLL]
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
I thought you were just
going to arrest them?
Sometimes people don't go quietly.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Hey. I'm glad you're both here.
We've got good news.
The white boys finally made
the drop in the desert.
They're gonna be here in a few hours
to make the exchange.
That is good news.
It gets better.
We got the recipe.
Gabriela's waiting for us.
We show her how to cook the rock.
the green light gets taken off.
We're gonna be free.
Pedro. I'm gonna need you to
come with me to Gabriella's.
Soledad. you and Gustavo stay
here to receive the shipment
and give Matt and Reed their cut.
Maybe Pedro and I should stay
here to take in the shipment.
Gabriella doesn't want anyone
who isn't family involved in this.
Gustavo isn't yet.
You said you wanted to be back in this.
Help run things.
Or did you change your mind again?
No. of course I'll come.
Yeah.
_
Adiós.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Take care.
♪ ♪
You're driving.
Aquí?
It's the address Gabriella gave me.
She said there's a kitchen in the back.
What if this is a setup?
It's either this or we run.
And I don't want to run.
Do you?
- I'll go in alone if you want.
- Kay.
Put your hands up.
Turn around.
- Lucia. what the fuck?
- Do it.
You reach for that gun I
swear I'll shoot you.
What's going on. prima?
We have a problem. Pedro.
Your fiancée.
She's a cop.
LAPD. DEA. I'm not sure which.
No. that's not possible.
I don't have a doubt in my mind.
What I don't know for sure
is what side you're on.
Listen to me. I...
- I had no idea.
- How is that possible?
What do you mean? She's my fiancée.
Why...
Why would I...
How do you know that?
Because I have my fucking eyes open.
- I don't understand.
- Tell me everything.
How you met? Where?
Every fucking detail.
- I already told you.
- Tell me again.
Convince me. Pedro.
Sell it to me.
And maybe you'll live to watch
me torture it out of her.
You're wrong.
She's not LAPD.
She's DEA.
Out of the Dallas Office.
I know because that's
where we were introduced.
After I walked inside.
told them that my name was
Pedro Nava Villanueva.
that my family were drug smugglers
and I wanted to bring what
was left of them down.
Jesus. Pedro.
Are you surprised?
After what you did.
What you forced me to do?
After you betrayed me.
- and still I saved your life.
- It's incredible.
I did everything for you.
- I let you back in.
- It's incredible that after everything.
you still yourself as the righteous one.
At least I'm not a fucking rat.
You're worse.
You're a disease. Lucia.
A plague that destroys
everything you touch.
It's not your fault. though.
It's just what you become when you see
your sister murdered
right in front of you.
[GUNSHOT]
Struck a nerve there. huh?
You're gonna fucking burn
for everything you've done.
Maybe.
But you're going to live.
And every day you'll hear my voice.
And know that you became the monster
your father always feared you'd become.
[GUNSHOT]
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm